(Howard(knocking on bathroom door):)- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
(Amy:)I'm just breaking in
some new shoes.
- Very pretty.
- Thank you.
(Amy:)Did you know that women
wear high heels
(Amy:)to make the buttocks
and breasts more prominent?
(Leonard:)Hadn't really thought about it.
(Leonard:)Look.
Uh, sure. Very... prominent.
(Amy:)Please, Leonard, don't leer,
you have a girlfriend.
(Priya:)- Sorry.
- So, are you off to dinner
(Amy:)with Priya, Howard
and Bernadette?
(Leonard:)Yeah. How did you know?
(Amy:)I heard it at the mall,
(Amy:)when I was shopping
with my girlfriends,
(Amy:)'cause, you know,
that's kind of my life now.
(Amy:)Have a good night.
(Amy:)Try not to ogle my caboose
as I walk away.
- Hey, you.
- Hi.
(Leonard:)Hey, Raj, will you
be joining us for dinner?
(Raj:)The lonely guy
and the two happy couples?